Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, it's so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in what I do.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't wanna live ordinary lives.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in wonderland.
Vivi!
Who are you?
Ready? Aim!
No, stop it!
Fighting is not going to help anything!
I'm fine, Luffy.
It only graced my arm.
It's alright.
We won't land.
But can you please call us a doctor?
Our friend is dying from a
serious illness. I'm begging you.
Please help us!
Vivi!
You are not fit to be the
captain of this ship, Luffy.
Not everything can be fixed
by rushing to start a fight.
We can't get into a fight here.
Think about Nami.
What would happen to her?
Yeah, right.
I'm sorry about that.
Please help us!
Call a doctor!
Our friend needs you!
I'll show you to our village.
Follow me.
See, just ask politely.
Yeah, you're incredible, Vivi!
There is one thing I feel I
should warn you about, though.
The only doctor we have
here is actually a witch.
Huh?
A witch?
You've got to be kidding me.
Everything about this island is messed up.
What do you people call
this weird place anyway?
Actually, this land still
doesn't have a name.
An island without a name?
I didn't know that was possible.
A bear! Hurry, everyone!
Pretend to be dead!
A hiking bear.
He poses no threat.
Don't forget to bow.
It's proper manners.
Nice.
That's much better.
Now I can finally get back
to some real training.
I was getting sick of that modified training
that I had to do with my stupid injury.
Besides, just watching the
ship is boring as hell.
Maybe some ice water swimming will
help me clear up my head a bit.
This is the village where we live.
Its name is Bighorn.
Look at all the weird animals
walking around everywhere.
Yeah, this is snow country.
Look, Nami, we've made it
to a village with people.
We're here.
Thanks for the help, everyone.
If you're not a guard, you
can return to your work.
Are you completely certain that
you'll be all right here by yourself?
They are pirates.
I believe these people mean us no harm.
That's my hunch anyway.
You can trust me on that.
So what should we do now?
If Dalton says they're all right,
then I think we should believe it.
They do seem to be pretty harmless, huh?
Yeah.
All right, Dalton.
We'll leave them to you.
Even so, be careful, Dalton.
And call us again if you need anything.
You mean those men weren't
your land security forces?
No.
They're just ordinary citizens.
Come to my house for now.
Hey!
Look over there, Luffy!
It's one of those hiking bears!
Another one?
Hello, Dalton.
I heard that some pirates
landed on the island.
I hope everything is all right.
Yes, everything's fine.
There's nothing to be worried about.
Just want you to know, Dalton, I'm looking
forward to the election in two days.
Everyone I've talked to has said
they're going to vote for you.
I'm sure you're not serious about that.
I'm just an ordinary citizen, that's all.
You can use that bed over there.
I'm going to warm the place up.
I guess I should introduce myself.
My name is Dalton.
I'm the captain of the
island's security squad.
Please forgive our less
than friendly welcome.
Excuse me, but may I ask you a question?
Huh?
It's just that you look
familiar to me for some reason.
No, I just have one of
those faces, I guess.
Anyway, can you tell us more about this
doctor, or witch, if that's what she is?
Nami's fever's gone up to 107.
How long has she had it?
It's been several days, and
it just keeps getting higher.
I see.
She'll likely die if it gets any worse.
Yes.
But we have no idea what the illness
is, much less how to treat it.
We don't know how to help her.
We've got to find a doctor
as soon as possible!
Any doctor will do!
Where is this witch of yours?
The witch?
Do you see those mountains
outside the window?
Yeah, I noticed them earlier.
Supermassive Snowman!
And the feared snowman Snowzilla!
Ha ha!
Get in here before I kill you!
Those mountains out there are
known as the Drum Rockies.
Look closely.
Do you see the castle on top of the
tallest one, the one in the middle?
Castle?
That castle has lost its key. Much warmer.
Yeah, I see it up there.
What's so important about the castle?
That castle is where our land's
only doctor lives, Dr. Kureha.
She's the one who people
here call a witch.
What?
Of all places, why does she have
to live on top of a mountain?
We need to call her here right now.
Nami needs her help.
I'm sorry, but I'm afraid
there's no way to contact her.
You can't be serious.
What kind of a doctor is she?
Her skills as a doctor are
quite impressive, actually.
However, she's an eccentric old woman.
She's nearly 140 years old now.
140 no wonder she doesn't get
around much oh and one more
thing she likes pickled plums
what happens when people here get
sick or injured doesn't she help
them she comes down from the
mountain whenever she feels like
it she looks around for patients
she treats them then before she
leaves she takes whatever she
wants from their houses as
payment she doesn't sound like a
very nice lady it kind of sounds
like she's a pirate but how is
a woman as old as she is capable
of getting down that mountain?
it's an odd rumor around here?
several of the villagers
claim they've seen her at
night riding a sleigh of
some kind through the sky
they see her silhouette
when the moon is out?
that's the reason she is
thought to be a witch?
there are others who say
they've seen her with a
strange creature a creature
that none of them recognize?
See I knew it a snow monster where there's
snow there's gonna be snow monsters.
Oh, I knew there'd be one
I don't want to run into one.
Dr.
Kureha is the only doctor we have,
but she's still a woman I
would prefer to stay away from.
All we can do is wait for the next time
she decides to come down the mountain.
Really?
No, damn it.
We can't wait here for that long.
Nami is getting even worse as we speak.
Hey, Nami.
Nami, wake up now.
Luffy, you idiot!
What are you doing to her?
Hey, look, she's awake.
Here's the thing.
The only way to see the doctor
is to climb the mountain.
So we're going to have
to climb the mountain.
Are you crazy?
What about Nami?
How do you expect to get her up there?
Easy, she'll ride on my back.
That's only going to
make her even more sick.
What's the problem?
I thought we needed to hurry.
We do, but you'll never make it up there.
Look at how steep and tall that thing is.
I can do it.
Maybe you can, but climbing that
thing would be way too hard on Nami.
But look, even if we fall or
something, we'll land in snow.
That doesn't matter.
A foal like that would
kill even a healthy person.
Seriously, Luffy, she
has a really bad fever.
It's so high she's almost dying.
Don't you understand that?
I need to get over this
thing, and quickly.
We need to hurry for Vivi.
Come on, Captain.
Let's go.
That's what I'm talking about.
Leave it to me.
I can't believe this.
Now our navigator's as
crazy as our captain.
You know, you're in no shape
for a trip like this, Nami.
Are you sure you'll be okay?
It'll take you hours to get there.
Hey, old guy, give me
some meat for the road.
Meat?
Right, I'm coming too.
Listen, Luffy, be very careful.
You can't fall even once
or Nami is going to die!
Ah!
Not even once!
Hold still a second.
I need to make sure that this is tight.
Okay, you're all set.
I'm going to wait for you here.
If I came with you guys,
I'd only get in the way.
Yep, me too!
Alright.
Now you just hold on
tight to me, okay, Nami?
I guess you're set on going.
I'm not going to try to stop you,
but I will ask you to at least
climb up from the other side.
That way you can avoid the
loppins that are on this side
They're fierce carnivorous rabbits.
You run into a pack of them.
You're as good as dead.
Huh?
Really?
We've got to get up there.
We'll be just fine, right?
Yeah, fine.
You can't be serious You know how
easily those things can kill you?
Nah, we'll be all right.
Now hurry it up Sanji before Nami dies!
Don't say stuff like that you idiot.
Do you want to Jango us?
Are you sure they'll be all right?
Well, it's not really those
two we need to worry about.
Nami's the one in trouble.
I just hope her strength
can hold out long enough.
She's getting sicker by the minute.
Why are you standing there?
Come on inside.
It's cold out here.
Oh, no, that's really okay.
I want to stay out here. Me too.
I see.
Well, in that case, I'll join you.
We did once have some here on this
island you know some doctors however all
Of them left some time ago for certain
reasons few months ago we suffered a
Vicious attack and our country was
destroyed destroyed by pirates oh man The
whole country so that's the reason you
acted that way when we showed up yes
After the attack the word pirate still
terrifies everyone on this island I'm
sorry about the way we treated you.
Their group was small as well.
Only five people.
Their captain called himself Blackbeard.
Their power was so
incredible they destroyed our
entire country faster
than you would believe.
And there were only five of them fighting?
That's impossible.
Blackbeard?
What's more,
there are some here who actually believed
that it was good for the country.
What could possibly be
good about that happening?
That's crazy!
Who would Say something like that anyway?
Thank you.
I agree.
But they have their reasons.
The king who ruled here before
the attack was a horrible man.
His rule was despised
by all of the citizens.
Our country used to be known as Drum
Kingdom and our king's name was Wobble.
He was the worst king imaginable.
Yes, I remember him.
I know that man. Not Womple!
It feels like it's gotten a little colder.
The wind's picking up, too.
So why don't you think about
putting on some real shoes?
Even seeing your feet
like that is painful.
No way!
This is my police. Your police?
I think you mean policy.
Yeah, that's it.
So anyway, though, did you know this?
People in snow countries
never sleep at all.
Huh? Why?
Because if they do,
they'll freeze to death.
Don't be an idiot.
Everyone has to sleep sometime.
It's the truth.
Someone told me a long time ago.
Who, Usa?
No, I heard it in a pub in my village.
All right, then explain this.
What does that Dalton guy have a bed for?
I guess that's a good point.
Hey, maybe it's for when he dies!
That's ridiculous!
Okay, then.
Did you know this?
Women in snowy countries have
skin that's as smooth as silk.
How come?
Isn't it obvious?
Here, I'll explain.
When you get cold, you rub
your skin to warm it up, right?
It's always freezing cold in
snowy countries like this one.
So the women keep rubbing
their skin all the time.
and so it becomes all
white and silky smooth.
Okay, but then how come it's white?
Because the snow,
it's constantly falling all over
them, so it dyes their skin all white.
Deej, you're really dumb.
Did you know that?
Yeah, give me a break like
you're really one to talk.
You're becoming a pain in my ass! Really?
What was with that thing?
Nami, just hang in there
a little bit longer.
We're going to get you
to a doctor, alright?
Snow's getting really deep around here.
Hey, Luffy, try to run
more smoothly, will you?
You're just making it harder on Nami.
What are these things?
Well, they're big and they're
white, so they must be polar bears.
What's that?
You mean you know who Wapol is?
Know who he is?
We know more than that.
He's the pirate who attacked
our ship not too long ago.
But I was able to take care of him.
Now that I think about it,
I do remember him saying something
about heading to Drum Kingdom.
Yes, there's no question about it now.
I remember it clearly.
I'm sure I met him once at a monarch
meeting my father took me to.
I was still very young then,
but I remember it to this day.
A monarch meeting?
Who are you?
Oh, no, I, uh...
Well, the point is, we do know Wapol.
We ran into him yesterday,
when we were on our way here.
Yesterday?
Are you sure about that?
But then, I don't understand
what's going on here.
He said he was a pirate.
He didn't say anything about being a king.
He's just calling himself a
pirate as some kind of disguise.
In truth, Wapol is only
wandering the seas,
trying desperately to
return to this island.
So then,
Wapol and the people who were
on his ship with him were kicked
off the island because they
were no match for the pirates?
Is that what happened?
That's not it. No.
When it happened, when we were attacked,
Waple's army didn't even try to fight.
In fact,
the second he learned how
strong the pirates were,
Wapol grabbed his cronies
and ran like a coward.
He was the first one to abandon
the country and flee out to sea.
After that, the country
felt utter despair.
We were left behind by our king.
What sort of king would
do that to his country?
A king abandoning his people?
Just the thought of that
makes me absolutely sick.
Vivi.
You're exactly right.
The one good thing that came out of it,
though, was the end of
Waple's tyrannical rule.
The people who were left on this
island have come together now.
We're trying to create a new country.
So what we fear most right now is the
return of Wapol and his followers.
The return of his brutal rule.
We can't afford for him to come
back now with a country so unstable.
It would be the end of us we want to build
ourselves a new peaceful
nation on this island
Seriously, how can it move like that?
Is it a gorilla?
Oh, it's a polar bear It's a rabbit.
How did you go from gorilla to rabbit?
These must be the loppins that
Dalton was telling us about
Well, there sure are a lot of them.
Wubble, come quickly!
What is it now?
Have you found that pirate's ship yet?
No, that isn't it, Wubble.
At long last, we've
returned home. We have?
How many long months have
passed wandering the sea?
That's our homeland, it's Drum Kingdom!
It truly is!
I can't believe it!
Listen, Luffy.
Let's get going.
We have to make it to the castle
where the doctor lives and quickly.
I don't want you fighting
these guys, alright?
Why not?
Because Nami will be able
to feel every move you make.
She's too sick to be able to
handle something like that.
It would be too much.
She could die.
What?
Jeez, okay, then I
won't fight them at all.
But then...
What can I do, huh?
Just dodge!
Dodge, dodge and run!
But don't retreat!
That's a little difficult!
Launcher, shoot!
Dodging!
Damn, in this snow I can't get my
footing well enough to land a solid kick!
You're attacking all at once!
Head for the forest!
I'll cover you!
Go left!
We'll head to the mountains!
We need to get rid of them somehow!
It would take us hours to fight them
all off, but how do we shake them now?
For bunnies, these guys are tough.
We're in trouble.
Stop it!
What are you doing?
I told you not to attack, you idiot.
Just leave them to me. Sorry.
This is no time to be screwing around.
Sanji, we can go up from here.
Right, go on.
Wanna give me a lift?
Did you really have to taunt them? Sorry.
Run for the top of the mountain.
The snow's really
starting to pick up, huh?
Nami, please just be okay.
Hello, Dalton!
I was looking for you.
Bow to the bear.
What can I do for you?
I heard the newcomers were looking for Dr.
Kureha.
Yes, but the sick woman's friends have
already taken her up the mountain.
Oh, that's too bad, because I heard
the doctor's in Kokoro right now.
She's where?
Huh?
Tsunami and the other's already past her?!
Come on.
We've had enough of this crying already.
Just make him stop.
It's driving me nuts.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Hey, Tamachibi, what's wrong?
You hurt somewhere?
You need to stop crying
and tell me what's wrong.
You're upsetting the customer.
Tamachibi, say something.
If you don't stop crying,
you're going to go to your room.
It's the witch.
I can't find the witch.
And look at that.
She's got that weird
monster with her again.
That's it.
I've had enough of this. Well, well.
Doesn't sound like a very
nice father in there.
If a child is crying uncontrollably,
Chances are something is wrong
and he doesn't know what.
Stay there for now, Chopper.
So sorry about that.
It's... you.
So are you kids happy?
Doctor! Karoo!
Anyone want my secret to staying young?
No, we're fine, thank you!
I can't believe she's
really 140 years old.
I'll have you know I'm only 139.
Shall I treat the boy?
Wait, what? He's fine.
He isn't sick or hurt or anything, really.
Excuse me, doctor.
Let's go, chopper.
Wait, please come back.
I'm sorry.
This is my mistake.
I was aware that the doctor had come into
town from the mountain
in the last few days,
but I assumed that she'd left and
wouldn't be back for quite some time.
Don't worry about it.
This isn't your fault.
The problem here is how abnormally
strong Lupi and Sanji are.
Even if we go up the mountain after them,
there's no way we'd be
able to catch up to them.
If we are able to find the
witch in this Kokoa-wee place,
we just need to tell her to get back up the
mountain as quickly as she possibly can.
You're right. That's true.
We have no other choice.
Forgive us, forgive this land
for not having more doctors.
Don't say that this isn't something
that you need to be apologizing for.
Dalton, she's right about that.
Let's hurry.
It's my hands.
They hurt. Your hands?
All right.
How's this?
You see?
Now you've forgotten all
about your hands hurting.
What was that about?
What did you do to him?
Are you happy? You're happy. Good.
Now stay nice and quiet. Hey!
And you should calm down.
I only touched his leg,
and I did it very lightly.
I heard a terrible noise.
He has pain in his hands and legs.
He doesn't have a fever.
The swelling here on his leg is
from a purulent inflammation,
and it doesn't look good.
By now, the bone is surely infected.
Chopper, bring me some antibiotics.
Um, doctor?
Is he all right?
The key to curing this disease is
treating it before it can get too strong.
Don't worry, he'll live.
However, he did almost die. What?
Almost died?
We're gonna do a little operation, okay?
Wait, aren't you gonna use any anesthesia?
This is the anesthesia.
What the hell?
Now see how easy that was?
That's it for the treatment, or
the part you need me for anyway.
The rest is up to you.
Just make sure he rests and
keep his legs tightly bandaged.
Once they're bandaged, keep them ice down.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Now about my feet.
I'm all out of trash
bags and toilet paper,
so I'm taking all of those that you have?
along with all your food and plum wine.
In addition to that, I'll be taking
50 % of this restaurant's assets.
Chopper, take it all to the sled.
This is outrageous!
You can't take half my assets!
Don't even think about
giving her all that.
It's too much.
It's just crazy.
It's ridiculous.
It's way too much.
How dare you take
advantage of a sick person.
You should be ashamed.
You are a real doctor at all.
You're just a witch.
It's all right, Chopper.
They're just a bunch of
blabbering children. Old lady.
The pain.
It's all better now.
Thanks so much.
Well, it looks like your
son just gave me a nice tip.
So I'll reduce my fee to 49%.
I'll pay your price. Thank you.
Oh, yeah. Hey, kid.
This happiness you feel.
Don't you ever forget it.
Okay.
It's freezing out here my whole body is
beginning to go numb i feel more like a
popsicle than a human at the moment looks
like i have a lot more
training to do but if
i really concentrate i shouldn't be bothered
by even the coldest temperatures hey
Karoo want to come in with me it's a great
way to get your little bird body in shape?
I didn't expect to see
this many fish here.
Well, I've got more to do.
They coming?
No, it doesn't look like it. Oh, right.
I guess we lost them, huh?
Nope, we haven't yet.
They don't give up!
Why are they jumping up and down?
Maybe they're grouchy
because they're hungry.
I don't think so.
Wait a second.
Don't tell me...
Oh no...
We've arrived at last!
After all this time, I've
returned to Drum Kingdom!
I'm finally home!
Were they trying to pretend
to be a real military?
Bunch of idiots and amateurs.
What were they thinking
shooting at us like that?
Oh, my dear Drum Island!
Your towering majesty has grown
even more beautiful in my absence!
Chess, is the castle alright? Yes.
It looks just as good as when we left it.
It's perfect!
Ha ha ha!
What are we waiting for?
Let's go home, boys!
I'm done being a pirate. Ha!
I'm going to be king again!
Onward, Robson!
Robson, move!
Why are you just standing here?
Hey!
Get moving already!
Wumple!
We have a problem!
What's the matter now?
The pirates!
The ones from the other day,
their ship's over there!
What?
Not them!
What are the Straw Hat
pirates doing in my country?
How dare they come here after
pretending to not even know about it!
Does he not even care?
I had a very painful recovery! You!
Go kill those pirates now!
I demand it!
Um, actually, the ship
is empty, sir. Empty?
We don't know where they went!
You want to be executed?!
Our apologies, Wapol.
Please forgive him.
This man is just a useless subordinate.
Chess!
We took the liberty of inspecting the
footprints that led away from the ship,
and we have some information.
Indeed.
It looks as if the footprints
were headed toward Bighorn.
Very good.
That was absolutely brilliant.
In that case, we're headed on to Bighorn.
We'll stop there to fire a salute to
the restoration of Throck Kingdom!
Wait, what are you telling us?
You mean the witch left this
town just a few moments ago?
Oh, you've got to be kidding me!
This is ridiculous!
She left after she made
my sickness all better.
If you're looking for the
doctor, she's already left.
We have to find her.
Can you tell us where she was
headed when she left here?
I think I know.
I heard from somebody else
that she was headed for Giasta.
Giasta?
So where is that?
If we were going to Geasta from Bighorn,
we'd go in the opposite direction,
then we went to come here.
Oh, great!
We already passed her?
Ice skating is very popular there.
What does that have to do with anything?
Who cares about that?
Calm down, Usopp.
We need to get going to that town.
At this point, we really
don't have any time to lose.
Yeah, you're right.
Dalton!
I found you at last!
Yes, Carrot, but I thought
you were standing watch today.
What's the matter I can tell that you've
been badly injured tell me what went wrong
Every watchman except
for me they've all been
killed Dalton watch this
thing this submarine
Sailboat it came out of
nowhere and it attacked
us they killed every one of the watchmen
we Couldn't stop them who are they I don't
understand please explain
this please Dalton you
have to help Us we aren't strong enough to
fight them you have to
do something what's wrong
It was them it was wobble
wobble and his men they came
back what did he say what was back
That can't be true. Why is he here?
Hey, wait!
Dalton, wait!
I'm going to settle this once and for all.
In the end, I don't know if it
can really be called justice.
I may be just as guilty as you are, but
you're the one who will be punished.
Just wait!
I'm coming for you, Warpo!